economybookings.com 2016-12-31

# Information on the use of our website. | EconomyBookings.com

## Our website using

Using our website, you confirm your agreement with our specified privacy policy.

### Cookies

Our website, email messages and advertisements may limitedly use "cookies" in order to provide you better services. It allows us to know, which parts of the website people have visited and to recognize them, when they return to our site. But these "cookies" do not contain user's personal or credit card information.

### Personal Information and Email

We use visitors' contact information (name and Email) in the following cases:

  * __to verify the users' identity
  * __to contact them if there is a necessity concerning booking
  * __to send them useful information about our company, if they choose to opt-in to it
  * __opt-out function allows a user to unsubscribe from our Email Newsletters

### Third Party websites

"Economybookings.com" websites may contain links to third party websites and services. Our company is not responsible for its content and privacy practices.

### Security

If you make a booking through our system, "Economybookings.com" guarantees the safety of all your transactions. Our company provides solid security measures in order to prevent personal information loss and misuse. Your name, Email and credit card number will be encrypted by our highest level secure server. These servers are designed to store personal information and prevent it from unauthorized access. Only limited number of our staff have an access to view your personal information.
